when we're seeing images like this like that's literally a person being strapped to like one of
the carts at my storage unit space and they're like oh you you won't walk this how we're going
to treat you when we see images like this i believe that that is the constant effort to
desensitize us and i know that people have been saying that that's not unique however the
desensitization is because they are really trying to build a nation that has the same psychopathy
as israel and for what it's worth at one point the united states did have that same psychopathy
and that's part of what they're trying to bring back like when they talk about make america great
again they also mean like let's make america a bunch of psychopathic killers again remember
that this is the same country that had people throwing throwing things and holding up babies
with new black babies with nooses around their neck to to to little black children going to school
like this is a place that literally ate nat turner okay this is a place that was putting using black
babies for bait like they want a psychopathic nation they believe that's what's going to keep
this nation in power they believe this one that's what's going to allow uh for the rest of the world
to still have to bow down even though it's trying to make end roads to to stabilize this place so you
got to ask yourself what are you doing to strengthen your capabilities to not be caught up in that you
have been caught up in that by nature of simply just being here are you going outside in nature are you
flooding your space with empathy and joy like when i say the whole like you know we have to fight for
our joy like that's not just because we're like we can't let them take our happiness it's also because
like those endorphins those chemical releases of dopamine they are also active agents against you
having those same reactions to violent behavior like people who actually like get joy excitement etc from
violence that has something to do with how you were raised you have to do that rewiring that has
to be an active choice people who are literally getting joy from game hunting i learned today that
president teddy roosevelt killed over 11 000 animals bro 11 000 animals that means that his pathology was
that he got joy excitement from death so you got to really ask yourself like what what am i doing to
counteract that am i changing the music i'm listening to am i actually literally making choices to
activate my dopamine and my endorphins in a different way through exercise through different
types of interactions through different taking in different art different spaces etc yeah like these
are these are all revolutionary acts all of it and every single person is a revolution do you know
that you are a revolution or you're just a tool in someone else's what's it gonna be support a real one
like these are all of it and every single person is to do that and it's um but you do remember to
take the same time
o